

ANDRES FELIPE DEL CHIARO BRODMEIER

Frontend Developer & Geologist Universidad del Norte

+57 3135948642 - anchibro@hotmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/delchiaroa/ Barranquilla, Colombia

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Frontend web developer specialized in React with knowledge in JavaScript, TypeScript, third-party and libraries/frameworks such TailwindCSS, Redux, React Query and React Router. Fluent level of English and Spanish (mother tongue), and basic level in Portuguese. With skills in teamwork leadership. and analysis. I've worked one year as a mudlogger for Datalog SAS in oil and gas wells.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development 03/2023 – 08/2023 Universidad de Cataluña

B.S in Geology 07/2017 – 12/2021

Bogatá D.C, Colombia

Fundación Universidad del Norte Puerto Colombia, Atlántico, Colombia

High School Graduate 08/2011 – 06/2017

Colegio San José de Barranquilla Puerto Colombia, Atlántico, Colombia

ACHIEVEMENTS AND RECOGNITIONS

2017 – 2021 **Distinguished Student:** Universidad del Norte

02/2022 Graduate of Excellence Degree: Universidad del

Norte

07/2020 **Geology Roll of Honour:** Universidad del Norte

COMPLEMENTARY TRAINING

The Ultimate React Course 2023: React, Redux & More Obtained on 10/2023

Udemv

Mastering TypeScript - 2023 Edition Obtained on 09/2023 Udemy

Languages: English 07/2017 - 11/2018

Language Institute – Universidad del Norte Puerto Colombia, Atlántico, Colombia

Languages: English
02/2013 – 05/2016
Colombo Americano
Puerto Colombia, Atlántico, Colombia

SKILLS

LANGUAGE

English

Spanish

Portuguese

SOFTWARE

React

JavaScript

TypeScript

TailwindCSS

HTML

CSS

PostgreSQL

Redux

React Router

React Query

NodeJs

MATLAB

QGIS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

08/2022 – 08/2023 Mud logging geologist for Datalog SAS in oil and gas wells.

RESEARCH, PROJECTS AND/OR PUBLICATIONS

02/2020 – 12/2021 Sources of potable water in the Magdalena Department – Historical variation and climate change effect.

COLLEGE LIFE

05/2020 – 12/2021 Member of the CERUN student group as the Geology student representative.

10/2021 – 04/2022 International internship with the Mississippi State University.